=Born Again=
=Episode 19=
I do have a way.
It just depends on
whether you have the guts
and the appetite for it.
Ms. Lei, don't listen to her nonsense.
Nobody asked you.
Get lost.
Go buy up Red Star Steel's
internal shares
right now.
Use cash to drive the price down
to 60 or 70 percent of face value.
Buy as much as you can
get your hands on.
You'll be rolling in it
before you know it.
You're just bluffing.
Ridiculous.
Ms. Lei, those shares
are just waste paper right now.
Why would we buy them?
If I'm not mistaken,
your family is already
planning to do this.
What? Trying to get rich
behind Ms. Lei's back?
Hey, boy.
Trying to play dirty?
Tell me,
is what she said true?
N-No.
I don't care.
Transfer all the shares
you can get to me,
at the price
Xiaotang named.
Otherwise, I'll make you
regret having those hands.
Heard me?
Y-Yes.
Xiaotang, is this intel solid?
What? Don't you trust me?
Yes.
I trust you, of course.
If this really works out,
you'll be the leader here.
I have no interest in being the leader.
Just don't break the law.
Deal.
I'm off then.
What are you waiting for?
Move!
Farewell to Xiaotang.
- Take care, Ms. Xiaotang.
Gu Xiaotang,
so you really can predict the future.
Of course. Believe me now?
Then what about them?
Don't worry.
I will never let them
do anything illegal.
To be honest,
I noticed you've changed recently.
You seem different.
Me?
You might not believe it.
To you,
I have changed into who I am
in a few days.
But to me,
she already feels very far away.
I do have changed now.
But I changed because of you.
It is you who have been with me.
When I was at loss
and couldn't find the way out,
you never gave up on me.
Sometimes I think,
if the loop never ends,
with you by my side,
it seems less terrifying.
What's going on?
Probably a short circuit.
Your heart is racing.
Is it always racing like this?
Do you really have a crush on someone?
Who is she? Do I know her?
Is she a classmate of ours?
- Come on, tell me.
- N-No one.
I remember now.
You told me about
a crush in high school.
So your regret is
not confessing to her?
Ye Shen.
Look, I'm pretty capable now.
So if you need my help,
just let me know.
I'll help you with anything.
Ye Shen.
I'll do anything for you.
Will you really do anything for me?
Of course.
But you'd better hurry
and seize the chance.
If I get back one day,
I won't be able to help you.
It'll be too late then.
Gu Xiaotang!
What is it?
I like...
What did you say?
I said...
I got it.
I'm leaving. Go home then.
See you tomorrow.
(Let's take a photo.)
Look at the camera.
Three, two, one.
Cheese!
Does my makeup look good today?
Not bad.
Is there anything different
from yesterday?
You lost an eyelash.
To the rightful owner.
Mom, I'm home.
What's for dinner?
Where's the money?
Where did you hide it?
- Mom?
- Don't think I don't know.
Ms. Lei told me
my debt is all paid off!
- Did you hide money from me,
- Mom!
and didn't pay off my debt?
- I'll call the police.
- Want to get me killed?
You're back just in time, you brat!
Tell me, did you hide the money?
Give it to me right now,
- You animal!
- or I'll beat you!
You animal!
Don't you dare hurt my mom!
- I'll kill you!
- How dare you!
How dare you fight back?
I'll beat you to death!
Stop it!
I'll fight you!
Mom!
Let me tell you,
paying off my debt
doesn't make you king.
Tell me!
How much money did you hide?
Where did all that money come from?
You must have more.
Give it all to me.
If you don't,
I'll beat you every single day.
How dare you hide money from me!
Bah!
Mom.
Mom, I'm calling the police.
Listen to me.
Sweetheart,
listen to me.
He's a ruthless thug.
Once he gets out of jail,
he won't let us live in peace.
Please don't call the police.
Endure it.
Just for a little longer.
- Mom.
- Just endure it.
But for how long?
Mom!
Wake up, Mom!
(In operation)
Any family of the patient?
- Any family here?
- Doctor.
Are you her family?
She suffered a major head injury
and has a mild concussion.
But that's not the main issue.
She has been overworked
and stressed for long.
Her heart and liver had
major underlying issues.
This severe trauma
triggered acute heart failure.
Her condition is critical.
She needs to be sent to the ICU.
Doctor,
please.
Please save her.
No matter what,
please save her.
We'll do our best.
But prepare for the worst.
(In operation)
(Is the past tragedy
going to repeat itself?)
(Wait.)
(I wasn't home when Mom died back then.)
(Perhaps she didn't die of illness.)
(She might be...)
(Su Dawei,)
(I will make you pay.)
Hello, Xiaotang.
Ms. Lei,
you said you'd do anything for me.
Does that still count?
Of course, yes.
Xiaotang, just tell me
what you want me to do.
♪The face deep in the heart♪
♪Suddenly clear and hazy♪
♪Across time and space, eyes meet again♪
♪Deeply trapped in the vortex♪
♪Searching for familiar outlines♪
♪Persistently guarding,
endlessly cycling♪
♪Even for just a second♪
♪If raindrops flow backward
into the sky♪
♪And sunlight reverses♪
♪As the sun rises and sets,
we reunite with yesterday♪
♪I'll build a dream with you♪
♪Upon the ruins, spring breeze arrives♪
♪Even if there's no end,
I won't regret the start♪
♪Eternity like a day, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to recognize my eyes♪
♪Following the tracks
of the days that were♪
♪A day like a lifetime, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to remember my name♪
♪I'll be the dawn you haven't seen♪